日本語字幕仕上げ：miraku  光荣字幕组（www.koeigame.cn）
Yes!
よっしゃ！
Alright!
Consecutive wins!
連勝！
ETU. Their first victory on home soil.
ＥＴＵ　本拠地　初勝利ね
では改めて
My name is Youtarou Natsuki.
夏木陽太郎　めでたく　今日からＥＴＵに復活します！
I'll be rejoining ETU with immediate effect!
頑張ってんじゃねえか　オメエスタメンだしよ
You're working hard, aren't you?
You even made it into the starting line-up! You pushed Sakai down the pecking order, right?
堺さん押しのけてだろ？
You're really something!
やるなあ　お前
He's an optimist.
基本的にポジティブなヤツだからな
So even if he's worried, others wouldn't know.
悩んでても　周りに　そうは見えなかったりするんだろうが
達海さんが監督になってから夏木のヤツ
Ever since Tatsumi became manager, he's been calling me a lot.
おれやたらと俺に電話してきたよ
見てろ
みっ　見たか！
S-See that?!
I thought he just got back from rehab!
ど…　どこがケガ明けだよ
I'm screwed. Can I still retain my position?!
ヤベエ　俺　レギュラ大丈夫か？
United we stand, Fly a flag!
United we stand,Fly a flag 風を受け止めて
kaze o uketomete
風を受け止めて
Let the wind blow through you
United we stand, Fly a flag!
United we stand,Fly a flag たなびけ勝利のflag
tanabike shouri no flag
たなびけ勝利の flag
Let the victory flag trail in the wind
haruka na gooru o shinjite
遥かなゴールを信じて
Believe in the goal that lies in wait and keep running
遥かなゴールを信じて 走り続けていて
hashiri tsuzuketeke
走り続けてけ
hibi yume tsumugu monotachi e furisosoge hikari yo
日々夢紡ぐ者達へ降り注げ光よ
Let light pour down upon the weaver of dreams
日々夢紡ぐ者達へ 降り注げ光よ
ase wa uragiranaitte kuchibiru kamishime
汗は裏切らないって唇噛み締め
Your sweat won't betray you, so bite down on your lips
汗は裏切らないって 唇噛み締め
nandomo tachiagari daichi o kakenukeru
何度も立ち上がり大地を駆け抜ける
And stand back up again and again as you dash across the earth
何度も立ち上がり 大地を駆け抜ける
yume ni owari wa naitte me o kagayakase
夢に終わりはないって 目を輝かせ
Our dreams never end, so keep on shining
Let's start now GIANT KILLING!
For the right! Hold on tight!
for the right
hold on tight
My story...
my story…
forever
Forever...
5th League Match
Yokohama Mariners vs ETU
横浜！　横浜！横浜！　横浜！　横浜！
ＥＴＵ！　ＥＴＵ！ＥＴＵ！　ＥＴＵ！　ＥＴＵ！
おい！さっきから焦りすぎだぞ　世良！
Hey, you were too rash on that one, Sera!
Dammit... And I thought I got that one right.
くっそ　今のはギリギリ抜けたと思ったけどなあ
I haven't got any good balls today.
今日は　全く　いい形でボルもらえてねえぞ
Only 30 minutes left?
もう　あと３０分かよ…
It's not easy to get past this guy.
なかなかウラ取れねえ
１０番のマク　外すなよ！
Keep a high line, defense!
ディフェンスライン　下げるな！
うん…　ここまで来ても集中を切らせないな　横浜
We've been playing for a while now, but Yokohama's focus haven't wavered.
I was expecting them to tire out by now.
そろそろ　だれてくると踏んでたんだけど
Though Sera's working hard, the opponent's defense line is pretty high.
世良も頑張っているとは思うのですが
ディフェンスラインの集中力が依然　高いですよ
What's more, they've completely contained Prince.
それに　何より王子へのマクが徹底してますね
They changed their formation just to shut him down.
好調の王子を　布陣　変えてまで封じに来るとは
He can't touch the ball at all.
全然　ボル触らせてもらえませんよ
Even during his playing days, Motoki's defensive capabilities have always been good.
もとき元木さんねちっこい守備してたからなぁ
Though I always managed to run circles around him.
まっ　俺はかわしまくってたけどね
I'm not going to lose to you, Tatsumi.
お前には負けねえぞ　達海
ETU's playmaker has always been Gino.
ＥＴＵのゲムメカはやはりジノだ
Once we mark him out, your attacks will be significantly reduced.
ここを抑えれば 攻撃のバリエションは減る
ワントップの世良には高さがあるわけではないし
Although you have a lone forward in Sera,
he has neither the height nor the ability to conjure something special.
ましてや　個人で状況を打開するほどの力もない
We still need to be careful of attacks being launched from the back,
気を付けなければいけないのは ウラへの飛び出しだが
but if Gino is shut out, they won't be able to create chances.
出しどころのジノが　抑えられていては
チャンスを作るのも容易ではないだろう
だが…
However...
When will those guys get thrown in?
いつ　あいつらが出てくるか
He's totally lost interest.
完全に　やる気なくしてますよ下げますか？
Should we take him out?
But then, he'll get annoyed and complain because he can't swallow his pride.
でもプライド高いから面倒なんですよねぇ
ETU have won two league games in a row.
ＥＴＵは　公式戦２連勝中横浜は
明らかにＥＴＵを研究し 守備を固めている
It's obvious that Yokohama did their homework on ETU and tightened their defense.
I guess a team will get analyzed more if they are doing well.
やはり　調子のいいチムは それなりに研究される
ETU only had 5 shots at the goal since the game started.
ＥＴＵはここまでシュトは　わずか５本
Sera and Akasaki each had a shot.
枠内は世良と赤崎が１本ずつ
Since the second half,
ほった後半から出た堀田が
Hotta has roughly been able to carry out Gino's job,
マクの厳しいジノの近くでは 何とかボルを運んではいるけど
but their attacks are lacking in variety.
今ひとつバリエションのある攻撃ができない
The reason for that is...
その原因は
紛れもなく…
Quickly! I have to pass it quickly!
速く…　速くパスしないと
椿の不調
...that Tsubaki is playing badly.
どこまでムラがあるのよ あいつ
How inconsistent can he be?
How many mistakes have you been committing, Tsubaki?!
イジミス多いよ 椿！
Focus, focus!
集中　集中！
あれって…
Ah, that...
吾郎さんが言ってた
Um, Goro, that's the amazing Tsubaki you were talking about, right?
椿っていうすごい選手だよね？
あ　いや　ええと…
Uhh... Well,
Come on, show us your true self, Tsubaki.
いいとこ見せてくれよ　椿
You were fantastic against Nagoya!
名古屋戦はキレまくってたじゃんかよ！
落ち着け　椿うっ！
Calm down, Tsubaki.
難しい事やれって言ってんじゃねえだろ
We're not asking you to do something difficult.
は　はい！
Y-Yes!
I thought that he had learnt to handle pressure during the Nagoya game,
名古屋戦のプレで　
プレッシャから解放されたと思ったが
むしろ　その逆か
but it seems otherwise.
相手からは警戒
The opponents are watching him, and the team has expectations...
味方からは期待
I guess a new kind of pressure is awaiting for him.
待っていたのは新たなプレッシャか
He might have to fight that pressure forever.
あいつは　この先　ずっとそれと戦っていくのかもな
We still can't find a breakthrough.
中盤どうも打つ手に欠けるなぁ
I have to calm down.
落ち着け…　落ち着けよ
This is the time for a real forward, an ace, to score a goal.
こういう中でバシッと一発決めてこそ
本物のフォワドエスストライカだってんだ！
I'll do it. I'll definitely do it!
やってやる！　やってやるよ！
見てろよ　ナツさん！
Just watch, Natsu.
あれ？
H-He's gone...
い…　いねえよ
監督！
Manager, I'm all ready. I can go in at any time.
準備万端っス俺
いつでも行けますよ
I'm feeling good too! Really!
スゲエ調子もいいんス！
マジで多分
When I'm on, you will be shocked too.
監督も　腰抜かすと思うな
Hey, you can beg me as many times as you want, Natsuki.
あのさあ
何度来ても無駄だって　夏木
But I will not let you play today.
お前は今日　出さないってばえっ！
Why, manager?!
何でですか　監督！
If you put me on the bench, why not sub me in?!
ベンチに入れていてそりゃ　あんまりだ！
You're noisy, Natsuki!
うるさいぞ　夏木！
お前さあ
Say... Didn't you score a goal against Yokohama around this period of the game last year?
去年とおととし
この時期の横浜相手に ゴル決めてるだろ
Their manager is a very meticulous person.
向こうの監督
やたら細かい事まで気にするタイプだからさ
So I thought I'd bench you to give him a sense of precaution.
お前がベンチにいるだけで
向こうには　若干の危機感を与えられると思ってね
If you haven't noticed, he's been glancing at our area from time to time.
現にさっきからこっちをチラチラ見てるし
That's why you're on the bench. To be honest, it's the only reason.
それがお前のベンチ入りの理由…っつうか
それだけ
The only reason?!
それだけって…
Don't be so impatient, Natsuki.
焦んなって　夏木
You're still not match-fit.
お前は　まだ体が出来上がってねえ
でも　しっかりケガを治してきた
But your injury has healed. That's enough for now.
それだけで評価に値する
約束するよ
I promise you...
I'll prepare a stage where you'll come back with a bang.
お前が爆発できる場は 俺が　きちんと用意してやる
Be patient and wait until then.
それまで おとなしく待ってろ
はいっ！
Yes!
うっせっての　夏木！
You're too loud, Natsuki!
He appears not to care about you, but he actually does...
見てないようで 見てたり
考えてないようで 考えてたり 
I don't quite get what he's doing,
なんだかよく分かんねえけど
俺は嫌いじゃないかもな…達海監督
but I guess I don't dislike Tatsumi either.
Finally, a chance!
久々のチャンス！
Go, Kiyokawa!
上げろ　清川！
Kiyo, pass it to me!
キヨさん　俺！　俺！
Damn, I was free!
クソッ！
フリだったのに　俺
Alright, a corner. Move up, Sugie!
よし　コナ！
杉江　上がれ！
あやうく寝るところだったよ
Man, I almost fell asleep.
Mark your man!
マク外すな！
I'll mark Sugie; you take No. 20.
俺　杉江を見るから
お前　２０番頼むウス
いいさ
Okay.
高さじゃ勝てないんだから
Whatever. I know I can't win with my height.
I'll use my speed and rush in instead.
スピド生かしてニアに飛び込んでやる
王子ニアに頼みます　ニアに！
Please make it a short one, Prince.
ＥＴＵ！　ＥＴＵ！ＥＴＵ！　ＥＴＵ！　ＥＴＵ！
来い！
Bring it...
It's long!
あっ！ファだ！
Yes!
おっしゃ！
Nice work, Murakoshi!
よくやった　村越！
You're amazing, Koshi! Nice goal!
スゲエ　コシさん！ナイスゴル
I... wasn't involved in the build-up to the goal at all!
俺…
全然絡んでねえじゃん
Hey, you!
えい！
Sera!
世良！
Good job.
お疲れウス
Thanks.
I'm remaining upfield.
俺は　そこのトップに入るから
There isn't much time left; let's hold on to the lead.
残り時間は　あと少しだ
しっかり断ち切るぞ
お疲れ　世良ウス…
Good job, Sera.
Thanks.
今日もまた無得点かよ
Another game without a goal.
８試合出て　いまだワンゴルのフォワドなんて
It's embarrassing. I've played in eight games and only scored once.
ありえねえよな
I'm not contributing to the team at all!
チムに　全然貢献できてねえじゃん　俺！
At this rate, I'll get benched sooner or later!
このままじゃそのうち　スタメン　外れちまうぜ
Nice shot, Sakai. Pressurize them!
ナイスシュト　堺！
競り勝ってるぞ
Crap, crap, crap! I'm screwed!
ヤバイ…
ヤバイ　ヤバイ　ヤバイ
ヤバイよ　俺
Nice game!
ナイスゲム！
Great goal, Murakoshi.
よく決めてくれた　村越！
As expected of Mr ETU!
さすが　ミスタＥＴＵ！
Let's keep up the momentum.
この勢いのまま突っ走るぞ！
Let's win five in a row to make up for the five-game losing streak!
とりあえず開幕からの５連敗の分
５連勝して借り返そうぜ！
Sera, score a goal next time!
世良！
次はゴル決めようぜ！
どうしたの？　世良さん
What's wrong, Sera? You look more timid than usual.
いつになく小さく見えるぜ
よくやったよ
You guys did well. We've now won three in a row.
これで俺たちは３つ続けて勝った
You guys should feel more confident about yourselves.
自信持っていいと思うよ
We didn't really cruise through today, but what matters is the result.
内容が良かったとは言いがたいけど
それでも勝ったことが大きい
The opponent was a tough one too.
相手も強かったしね
反省会は　また明日とりあえず
We'll review the game tomorrow.
Get some rest for now... except for Tsubaki.
ゆっくり休もう
ただし　椿！
You'll have an individual review now.
お前だけ　個人反省会
Y-Yes.
You've been singled out!
呼び出しだ
呼び出しだ！
Being scolded is the best, Tsubaki.
怒られてるうちが華だぜ　椿
ホントだぜ　代えられなかっただけマシだと思えよ
Yeah, you should be glad that you weren't subbed off.
バッキのお陰で
Thanks to Baki, we blew up quite a few chances.
いくつか決定的なチャンスが　つぶれたからね
王子…
Prince, that was too direct.
バッサリ言いすぎ
Come on! Get a move on, Tsubaki!
早く行け　椿！
Y-Yes.
はい
I bet everyone feels the same way about me.
みんな
みんな椿に思ってるようなことを
きっと俺にも思ってるんだ
クソ
Dammit! If only I'd scored back then...
あそこで決めてれば！
Tsubaki gets scolded because he's capable of doing amazing stuff,
椿は時々　すげえプレするし
so there are expectations,
期待されてるから怒られるんだろうけど
but I won't even be yelled at.
俺は怒られもしない
I know why.
理由は分かってるさ
みんなは待ってるんだ
Everyone's expecting the return of Natsu, the first-choice forward.
ナツさんていう本命のフォワドが出てくんのを
And today, Sakai went in and took a nice shot.
それに　今日　堺さんも途中出場で
決定的な場面を作ってるし
They must be expecting me to be benched again soon.
俺はまた　ベンチに引っ込むと思われてるんだ
What's up, Sera? You're dazing away!
どうした　世良！
元気ないぞ
Are you a kid? Getting all sleepy like that...
子供じゃあるまいし
もう　おねむか？
We just won!
せっかくの勝ち試合だ
Cheer, laugh, sing!
喜べ！
笑え！
歌え！
何スか　ナツさん？
What's with you, Natsu? Coming out of nowhere...
いきなり
We won three in a row... Three!
３連勝だぞ　３連勝！
He doesn't know how I feel...
人の気も知らないで
俺が復活したら　バンバン　ゴル決めて
When I'm back, I'll score goal after goal and extend our winning streak!
更に連勝　伸ばすからな
What's with this guy?
何なんだ　この人？
おい　夏木
Hey, Natsuki.
Yes?
Quit fooling around in the bus. You'll-
バスの中ではしゃいでると　お前　そのうち…
What are you doing, Natsu?
何やってんスか　ナツさん
オラ　座れ夏木　
Natsuki, sit down or you'll hurt yourself again.
またケガすんぞ
True!
そうっスよ またやったらしゃれにならないっスよ
No. No, no, no! I don't want to lose...
嫌だ…
嫌だ　嫌だ　嫌だ
俺は　こんな人に…
負けたくねえ！
...to someone like him!
I must score for our next game.
次の試合こそ絶対　点　取ってやる！
But, will I still be starting?
でも　俺
スタメンで出られるのか？
Huh?
Oh yeah!
おっしゃ！
Huh?
あれ？　俺　スタメン大丈夫か？
Is my starting position safe?
Meeting room
Non-ETU personnel
Out of Bounds
This is the formation Shimizu's expected to use.
これが　予想される　今日の清水のフォメションだ　
Well, it's likely they'll use the same formation as they did for our last two meetings.
まあ　間違いなく 前回　前前回と同じ布陣で来るだろう
相手選手の特徴…
I want to start, I want to start, I want to start!
Keep their strengths and style in mind before anticipating their moves.
スタメンで出たい！スタメンで出たい！スタメンで出たい！
その次のプレを常に予測して動け
ウス！
Natsu has gotten better, but it's uncertain if he'll actually play yet.
ナツさんは大分　調子を上げてきてるけど
実際に出るかどうか微妙っぽい
今日は俺か堺さんだろう
So it's either Sakai or me.
And today's starting line-up is...
で　うちのスタメンは…
Goalkeeper: Dori.
ゴルキパ　ドリ はい
Yes.
ディフェンダ　石浜  はい！ スギ  クロ キヨ
Defense: Ishihama.
Yes.
Sugie.
スタメン来い　スタメン来い　スタメン来い！
Starter, starter, starter, starter!
Yes.
Kuro.
Kiyo.
Yes.
Midfield: Murakoshi.
ミッドフィルダ　村越　椿　赤崎  ジノ　丹波
Yes.
Tsubaki.
Akasaki.
Yes.
Gino.
Come on, come on, come on.
来い　来い　来い　来い！
Tanba.
Yes.
And as for the forward...
で　フォワド…　世良
Sera!
Yes!
はいっ！
Reserve: Sakai.
リザブ　堺クウ
Yessssss!
Yeah, I'll do it! I'll score today for sure!
よっしゃ！
やってやる！
今日は　絶対　点取ってやる！
4th round of the Japan Cup Prelims
Shimizu Impulse vs ETU
Don't let him pass! Kiyokawa, don't lose out in one-on-one situations!
行かせんじゃないぞ！１対１で負けんな　清川！
どこまで　ガツガツ攻め込んでくんだ　こいつら！
How long are they going to attack like this?!
He's shooting!
打ってくるぞ！
あっぶねえ！
That was close.
Nice save, Dori!
ナイスセブ　ドリ！
Put it out for now, Kiyokawa!
いったん切れ　清川！
Man, how many times did they shoot already?
これで向こうのシュト何本目だ？
リグ戦とカップ戦
Both the league and the cup match...
今期　清水はウチに既に２回も勝ってるからね
Shimizu have already defeated us twice, so they're getting cocky.
調子に乗ってやがんだ
On the contrary, we're not moving fluidly, subconsciously thinking ourselves to be the inferior team.
逆に　こっちは動きが硬い
もう苦手意識が　できちまってる
弱いチムの負け癖はふっしょく
The losing mentality of a weak team is not that easy to forgo.
そんな簡単には払拭されない
得点どころか 
We're so busy defending that I can't even think of scoring.
ディフェンスばっかで
全然シュトまでいかねえじゃねえか
Damn!
ナツさんは今日もベンチの外だ
Natsu isn't on the bench today.
I don't want to lose to Sakai either.
堺さんにも負けたくねえ今日は
I must score today!
絶対　点を取る！
Gino!
ジノ！
あっぶないなあ
That was dangerous.
Sorry, Seri! I overhit that pass.
ゴメン　セリパスが長くなっちゃった
Come on, catch up to it!
追いつけ　俺！
Sera!
世良！
通ればチャンス！
A chance!
That's so close.
ああ　惜しい
Damn, I almost caught up to it.
クソッ！　もうちょっとで追いつけたのに
Let's go, Sera!
いいぞ　世良！
ナイスラン！
Nice run!
世良！　世良！　世良！
I need to concentrate. My chance will come soon.
集中切らすな　俺
必ず　またどこかで　チャンスは来る
Then I'll seize that opportunity and score the winning goal.
そのチャンスをものにして決勝ゴルをたたき込むんだ！
世良！　世良！
Their passes are getting slower.
ボル回しが遅くなってきた
やっと向こうも攻め疲れてきたか
They're finally starting to tire.
It's up to you!
頼むあ…
よし　奪った！
Great interception!
カウンタ！
Counter!
What should I do? Should I pass it back to Prince?
どうする？１回王子に戻すか？
Sera!
世良！
There it is! A nice pass.
来た　ナイスパス！
このワンチャンスここで
This is my chance!
I'll make it count!
行け！
He can reach it!
追いつける！
Shoot!
打て！
行けっ！
Here goes!
Damn!
クソ！
あ…　世良
Sera...
You've got find the way to believe
Carry on and carry on
carry on and carry on
Till you can see tomorrow
I'll say “never look back”
I'll say 「never look back」
oikaze o matte
追い風を待って
Wait for the tailwind
sou chance o nogasunara
そう chance を逃すなら
And if you missed the chance
そうchanceをのがすなら
jibun ga kaze ni nare
自分が風になれ
Become the wind yourself
自分が風になれ no fears no tears
No fears! No tears! Yes! Let it go!
no tears,Yes Let it go！
Get tough! Get tough!
Get tough！(Stay gold！)
Stay gold!
Get tough！(We'll go！)
We'll go!
genkai oikose yuke
限界追い越せ行け
Surpass your limits and go!
限界追い越せ
行け キツイほど
kitsui hodo heart in red
キツイほど　heart in red
The harder it is the redder your heart will be!
heart in red
Go on! Go on!
Go on！(Stay cool！）
Stay cool!
We'll go!
Go on！(We'll go！)
asu wa mienai dakara
あすは見えないだから
Because we can't see into the future
あすは見えない だから
It's time to go yamerarenai
It's time to go やめられない
So it's time to go. We can't quit!
It's time to go
やめられない
Get tough!
Get tough！Get tough！ Get tough！
Get tough! Get tough!
Get tough！(Stay gold！)
Stay gold!
Get tough！(We'll go！)
We'll go!
tomo ni norikoete yuke
共に乗り越えて行け
Let's get through it together
共に乗り越えて 行け
見えるか It's daybreak there
mieruka It's daybreak there
Can you see that it's daybreak there?
Go on! Go on!
Go on！(Stay cool！) Go on！(We'll go！)
Stay cool!
We'll go!
yosoku dekinai dakara
予測できないだから
The future is unpredictable
It's time to go tomerarenai
It's time to go 止められない
So it's time to go. We can't stop!
It's time to go
止められない
How's Sera doing?
He's always been noisy, eh?
I won't lose out!
It's a bit early, but I guess now's the time.
Natsuki's return foreshadows an event.